<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>HAMZEH&#39;S WEBPAGE</title>
    <link>https://hamzehkhazaei.github.io/</link>
      <atom:link href="https://hamzehkhazaei.github.io/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description>HAMZEH&#39;S WEBPAGE</description>
    <generator>Source Themes Academic (https://sourcethemes.com/academic/)</generator><language>en-us</language><copyright>@ 2019 Hamzeh Khazaei</copyright><lastBuildDate>Mon, 01 Jan 2018 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <image>
      <url>https://hamzehkhazaei.github.io/img/icon-192.png</url>
      <title>HAMZEH&#39;S WEBPAGE</title>
      <link>https://hamzehkhazaei.github.io/</link>
    </image>
    
    <item>
      <title>ECE422</title>
      <link>https://hamzehkhazaei.github.io/teaching/ece422/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://hamzehkhazaei.github.io/teaching/ece422/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://catalogue.ualberta.ca/Course/Details?subjectCode=ECE&amp;catalog=422&amp;previousTerms=True&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;&gt;&lt;span&gt;This course&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;
introduces students to software system reliability engineering and computer security, in two six-week
modules. In the system reliability module, we will examine the similarities and differences between reliability
engineering for hardware systems and for software systems, and techniques for achieving software reliability.
Software fault tolerance mechanisms will be the main focus. In the computer security module, we will examine the
potential threats to computer system security, and controls for protecting computer systems against both malicious
and non-malicious compromise. By its nature, computer security extends beyond the domain of software, and encompasses
the entire environment in which a computer system is embedded. Therefore, this module will examine both software and
non-software threats and controls.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>ECE720</title>
      <link>https://hamzehkhazaei.github.io/teaching/ece720/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://hamzehkhazaei.github.io/teaching/ece720/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;In &lt;a href=&#34;https://calendar.ualberta.ca/preview_course_nopop.php?catoid=28&amp;coid=241424&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;&gt;&lt;span&gt;this course&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;,
we investigate dependability attributes including performance, reliability,
availability, fault tolerance, security, maintainability and operation of distributed systems. We
study these topics from the analytical modeling point of view. Provided that, related theories
including stochastic processes, queuing theory, petri nets and machine learning algorithms will
be employed to quantify dependability measures of interest. As a result, students will learn how
to apply their learning in designing dependable distributed computing systems.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>EECS 3221</title>
      <link>https://hamzehkhazaei.github.io/teaching/ece3221/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://hamzehkhazaei.github.io/teaching/ece3221/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;This course is intended to teach students the fundamental concepts that underlie operating systems, including
multiprogramming, concurrent processes, CPU scheduling, deadlocks, memory management, file systems, protection and
security. Many examples from real systems are given to illustrate the application of particular concepts. At the end of
this course, a student will be able to understand the principles and techniques required for understanding and designing
operating systems.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>EECS 5XXX</title>
      <link>https://hamzehkhazaei.github.io/teaching/eecs5xxx/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://hamzehkhazaei.github.io/teaching/eecs5xxx/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Coming Soon.&lt;br&gt;
This is an introductory course in Distributed Systems. Distributed systems is the study of how to build a computer
system where the state of the program is divided over more than one machine (or &amp;ldquo;node&amp;rdquo;).&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
