<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>undergrad | HAMZEH&#39;S WEBPAGE</title>
    <link>https://hamzehkhazaei.github.io/tags/undergrad/</link>
      <atom:link href="https://hamzehkhazaei.github.io/tags/undergrad/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description>undergrad</description>
    <generator>Source Themes Academic (https://sourcethemes.com/academic/)</generator><language>en-us</language><copyright>@ 2019 Hamzeh Khazaei</copyright><lastBuildDate>Wed, 01 Jul 2020 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <image>
      <url>https://hamzehkhazaei.github.io/img/icon-192.png</url>
      <title>undergrad</title>
      <link>https://hamzehkhazaei.github.io/tags/undergrad/</link>
    </image>
    
    <item>
      <title>EECS 2011</title>
      <link>https://hamzehkhazaei.github.io/teaching/eecs2011/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Jul 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://hamzehkhazaei.github.io/teaching/eecs2011/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;This course discusses the fundamental data structures commonly used in the design of algorithms.
At the end of this course, students will know the classical data structures, and master the use of abstraction,
specification and program construction using modules. Furthermore, students will be able to apply these skills
effectively in the design and implementation of algorithms.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>EECS 3221</title>
      <link>https://hamzehkhazaei.github.io/teaching/eecs3221/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://hamzehkhazaei.github.io/teaching/eecs3221/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;This course is intended to teach students the fundamental concepts that underlie operating systems, including
multiprogramming, concurrent processes, CPU scheduling, deadlocks, memory management, file systems, protection and
security. Many examples from real systems are given to illustrate the application of particular concepts. At the end of
this course, a student will be able to understand the principles and techniques required for understanding and designing
operating systems.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>EECS 4222</title>
      <link>https://hamzehkhazaei.github.io/teaching/eecs4222/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://hamzehkhazaei.github.io/teaching/eecs4222/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Coming Soon.&lt;br&gt;
This is an introductory course in Distributed Systems. Distributed systems is the study of how to build a computer
system where the state of the program is divided over more than one machine (or &amp;ldquo;node&amp;rdquo;).&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>EECS 4415</title>
      <link>https://hamzehkhazaei.github.io/teaching/eecs4415/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://hamzehkhazaei.github.io/teaching/eecs4415/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Storing, managing, and processing datasets are foundational to both computer science and data science. The enormous size of today&amp;rsquo;s data sets and the specific requirements of modern applications, necessitated the growth of a new generation of data management systems, where the emphasis is put on distributed and fault-tolerant processing. New programming paradigms have evolved, an abundance of information platforms offering data management and analysis solutions appeared and a number of novel methods and tools have been developed. This course introduces the fundamentals of big data storage, retrieval, and processing systems. As these fundamentals are introduced, exemplary technologies are used to illustrate how big data systems can leverage very large data sets that become available through multiple sources and are characterized by diverse levels of volume (terabytes; billion records), velocity (batch; real-time; streaming) and variety (structured; semi-structured; unstructured). The course aims to provide students with both theoretical knowledge and practical experience of the field by covering recent research on big data systems and their basic properties. Students consider both small and large datasets because both are equally important and justify different trade-offs. Topics include: software frameworks for distributed storage and processing of very large data sets, MapReduce programming model, querying of structured data sets, column stores, key-value stores, document stores, graph databases, distributed stream processing frameworks.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
